{"data":[{"question":"Economic goods often consist to material items, but they can also be services to people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"goods","b":"to","c":"but","d":"be","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- To-> of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Moby-Dick is a novel that telling the story of a ship captain's single-minded hatred of a huge while whale.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"novel","b":"telling","c":"single-minded","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Telling-> tells","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Earwax lubricates and protects the ear from foreign matter such water and insects.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Earwax lubricates","b":"foreign","c":"such","d":"insects","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Such-> such as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Before creating the telegraph, Samuel Morse made their living as a painter.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"creating","b":"made","c":"their","d":"as","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Their-> his","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Some jellyfish make daily journeys from deep water to the surface and back, while others migrate horizontal.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"make","b":"from deep","c":"while","d":"horizontal","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Horizontal-> horizontally","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"To putting a large amount of information on a map, a variety of symbols must be used.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"To putting","b":"on","c":"variety","d":"must be used","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- To putting-> to put","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Before the nineteenth century it was rarely to find organized systems of adult education.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Before","b":"it","c":"rarely","d":"systems","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n-Rarely-> rare","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Smoking is the number one prevent cause of death in the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Smoking","b":"the","c":"prevent","d":"of death","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Prevent-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Not single alphabet has ever perfectly represented the sounds of any of Earth's natural languages.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Not","b":"perfectly","c":"sounds","d":"any of","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Not-> no","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The ozone layer must be protected because it shields the Earth from excessive ultraviolet radiate.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"must be protected","b":"it","c":"from","d":"radiate","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Radiate-> radiation","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}